when I saw people taking shots at Angel
Reese for crying because for the longest
time you know she is a young person do
you know how disgusting that is and that
cornball who loves to make himself
look like he's the white people savior
who said that emuel AO oh Lord have
mercy
corny oh Lord have mercy man come talk
to me white people I'm the black guy
that's that's nice cut it out it's
ridiculous man I know these people man
I'm going have to have well you're not
saying that I am you not saying it and
you don't you don't and I will let you
off the hook it you don't need to
respond don't feel like you need to
defend them I no no no but baby you
can't I'll let you have your space this
is your safe space to say your
peace can I have a
hug no you would give me no hug early I
Tred to get I try to get a d I have to
get to a hug and now I'm there I have a
hug yes you can have a hug
thank
you dang that
was that was that was quick I feel I
feel I feel good good I feel
good good you hosted the BET Awards in
2020 in my house and ain't been
back Shany let me tell you can't nobody
say you don't put it together that's why
you was so successful on the feet why
why ay nobody told you why why you ain't
been you can't host no more you can't
well the internet told me that I haven't
been back because I'm not
likeable baby I hosted the awards in my
house yes I'm not saying that lightly Co
M was happening and The Stylist uh their
assistant tested positive ended up being
a false positive but it tested positive
and two days before I had to host the BT
Awards in my house wow I find this out
now at the time somebody I had been
seeing
on and off we were going to try to see
if we get along again so you going to
let him come he going to stay for an
extended period of time cuz Co so he was
already he was coming to the house and
we're literally sitting next to each
other when I get this call from Jesse
Collins shout out to Jesse Collins and
Deon Harman these are two people that
are two of the most beautiful human
beings on the earth and Jesse Collins
helped break the code for me about me
Jesse Collins without calling me
autistic knew I was before I knew I was
and he literally told told the staff
this is how Amanda Works she needs
information that's what she needs lots
of it she just needs the information and
when she has the information she's fine
right so let's just give her that it
doesn't take anything away from us but
some people feel like giving information
is like some power struggle type
right but he tells me this
Shannon so this man B James is at my
house and he's like I don't do physical
labor I'm like Lord child
so I get him a check I get him a check
to do the the show to to put up to put
this thing together um one thing I'll
never take from that man is he put that
he he did hook up them wires okay yeah
but now I can't have a stylist a hair
stylist or makeup artist here so I end
up having to do my own makeup with my
makeup artist on my phone my my hair
with my hair stylist on like they're all
on FaceTime telling me what to do I did
13 costume changes in my house while
this man sat in my backyard on FaceTime
telling people yeah I saved the BET
Awards and I got him a credit because
that's the type of I am I got him
a credit and I got him his check now did
he I'm not even let me stop but I but
you see how I'm protecting people that
don't protect yeah yeah yeah you see how
I about to do that cuz he the type of
person that would take things to another
level he tried to extort me
once you've been having a rough go with
me I know because I didn't have a father
that really taught me what to do and
because I I I present to people in a way
that they deem masculine but it's really
just passion and if they really were
smart they would understand that the
passion that I speak with is the passion
that I F with so I don't understand why
they can't do that
math yeah Sports I was reading
that I I read that you I read that you
know about what a nickel defense is in
football I don't even remember anymore
don't put me on the spot but I really um
you love sports huh or you love football
or you love the me no I appreciate
Sports the sports that I I mean like I
it wouldn't be fair to say I love
football because it's not even close to
my love for gymnastics okay you know I
respect football I respect basketball I
mean I'm I got a Jay you know I got I
used to have handles in my younger days
now I have back
problems but well that what what you was
saying about earlier that that's the
kind of same thing that you was able to
do with back problem you ain't going to
be able to do that no more man so think
you have to sit there when
I I think it's all about
creativity I'm sorry I brought that up
you talking to a comic like whatever you
say I got something in the chamber you
know that's the other part I'm a really
good mother comic did you know that I
did know that I didn't know that yeah I
didn't know that okay well I mean I have
my special you know I have my special I
be knowing but this year is when I
really realize like you nice with
this I've been going on stage and I
don't even prepare no more I just go to
see right baby I'm killing you like that
huh I'm really well how about this
here now not to say not to say I haven't
had my L's yeah I there was a particular
room in Los Angeles that I did take an L
but I have a different style of Comedy
than that room was expecting right
dating in
2024 I am
single you ain't try you ain't who's
hollering at me Shannon who's who is
hollering at me who let me ask you this
how about this here at this point what
type of man are you what type of man
would interest Amanda does he have to
be scholarly uh funny I mean women like
funny so that needs to be one women like
funny he has to have character character
and when I say character I mean has to
have a very strong value system okay he
has to care about Humanity okay he has
to like animals okay he has to um like
music okay uh he has to be curious he
doesn't have to be scholly but he has to
be curious okay and and the thing about
curiosity is it's not just about like
education but you have to be able to be
curious about somebody else's feelings
you know like that's the thing I feel
like I I run into with a lot of men like
they they not curious about like if I
say I'm sad or if I'm saying annoyed
like they go into defense but really the
next question should be
why why and then there a conversation
and I learned in my last relationship I
really really worked on my toxic traits
you know because we're all working to
undo the things that shaped us that we
had no control over toxic huh I was yeah
we all
are anymore you definitely have toxic
trait whoa whoa Amanda this is not about
me not be me okay thank you this man
said I need to every morning I'm like
whoa whoa whoa whoa you didn't say that
to ooo you didn't say that to ooo you
didn't say that to ooo I said I don't
know if I is that
toxicity get a mean because the way you
framed it I'mma just say I'mma just say
sh I'mma just say sh Shay the way you
had said it was like whether she likes
it or not this is my expectation and
sometime the ain't Prime until
prime time and it's just like damn is
that what the expectation is every
morning I mean sometimes my pockets
ain't Prime but she expect that b
nothing about I can't speak to that that
sounds like an escort yeah I'm just
saying that sounds like pros I'm just
saying you know sometime I hate Pride
that sounds like got how about this so
you me to tell ain't no man I know they
sliding in your DM they're not ain't no
man in your DM no have a been there was
one person in my DMs but they they're
not really like into me they're just
like talking about professional stuff
whatever ain't nobody sliding no DM I
don't know I don't know if he has a girl
I'll ask you Offa they sliding your DM
I'll ask you off
camera
[Music]
Lord no they don't slide my DM because
they're like she's too intense right and
that's the thing I feel like a lot of
men holler at me because they want to
tame me like they they like it's like a
game for them yeah and like I had a dude
I was talking to who was like yeah you
know I like you because you're a
challenge don't I don't want to do none
of that I don't want disc course I want
intercourse like
please I want to be home on the couch
hug the boot up that's really what I
don't want to fight people be like
Amanda seals in her tone I'm talking to
a phone baby I'm talking to a phone I'm
not talking to you I'm talking to a
phone and if I say these idiots and you
take offense to
that well that's your fault want to join
Club sh Shay become an official member
by hitting that subscribe button where
you never know who's going to be joined
us for drinks and conversation don't be
late to the party because you know we
like to do something before to something